(Past Howard:)I haven't seen your Oreos!
(Past Howard:)Just take your bath without them!
(Penny:)So why was it his lucky day?
(Leonard:)It turns out I had a little rocket fuel
in the apartment.
(Penny:)What were you doing with
rocket fuel in your apartment?
Joyce Kim was curious
about what I did for a living...
...and I was gonna
kind of show it to her.
(Leonard:)The point is, the guys and I
went back to the apartment.
-Are we ever gonna get to the elevator?
-We're close. We're at the apartment.
(Past Leonard:)The trick is to mix it into Tovex in
order to create a combustible gel...
(Past Leonard:)...that will generate over
8000 kilonewtons of thrust.
(Past Raj:)-Cool.
-Nice.
SHELDON:
Won't work.
(Past Leonard:)Excuse me, but I've been
working on this a long time.
(Past Leonard:)Trust me, it'll work.
(Past Sheldon:)You don't see your mistake, do you?
(Past Leonard:)There's no mistake.
This is for a full scale rocket,
not a model.
(Past Leonard:)-Well, I've adjusted the formula.
-Not correctly.
(Past Leonard:)Okay, I've had it with you.